Ryan Hull

San Francisco Bay Area

ryandelonhull@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/ryan-hull-94003144

Summary

I have experience managing people, setting schedules, working with clients, and enforcing maintenance standards in the retail industry. I have IT experience for a state health department working with health care workers and officials. I have more experience with customers in the restaurant industry.

I am currently learning coding in a bootcamp from UC Berkeley and can't wait to get my career off the ground in the tech industry.

Experience

Currently in a Coding Bootcamp at Berkeley University

Freelance

Sep 2020 - Present (2 months +)

Taking a chance at a career change into the tech industry thanks to covid.



Maintenance

Supervisor

Nordstrom

Aug 2019 - Sep 2020 (1 year 2 months)



Maintenance

Specialist

Nordstrom

Jul 2017 - Aug 2019 (2 years 2 months)



Operations

Consultant

State of Florida

Dec 2010 - Aug 2019 (8 years 9 months)

Education



Jacksonville

University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Sociology

Skills

Microso⊠ Office • Microso⊠ Excel • Microso⊠ Word • Customer Service • PowerPoint • Photoshop • HTML • JavaScript • AJAX • CSS